office_questions = [
    {
        'question': 'What item of Dwights did Jim put into jello?:',
        'answers': ['a) Pen',
                    'b) Phone',
                    'c) Stapler'],
        'correct': 'c'
    },
    {
        'question': """What game does Angela tell Pam she
        likes to play in the office?:""",
        'answers': ['a) Jim Ball',
                    'b) Pam Pong',
                    'c) Micheals Mission'],
        'correct': 'b'
    },
    {
        'question': 'What item of Andys did Jim put in jello?:',
        'answers': ['a) Wallet',
                    'b) Stapler',
                    'c) Calculator'],
        'correct': 'c'
    },
    {
        'question': 'How many years were Roy and Pam engaged for:',
        'answers': ['a) 1',
                    'b) 2',
                    'c) 3'],
        'correct': 'c'
    },
    {
        'question': """What word did Dwight have taped to his
        head for "Diversity Day":""",
        'answers': ['a) Black',
                    'b) Asian',
                    'c) Jewish'],
        'correct': 'b'
    },
    {
        'question': 'What is the perfume that Phylis wears made out of?:',
        'answers': ['a) Cedar',
                    'b) Real Pine',
                    'c) Sandal Wood'],
        'correct': 'b'
    },
    {
        'question': 'What is Gabes last name?:',
        'answers': ['a) Susan',
                    'b) Gabriel',
                    'c) Lee'],
        'correct': 'a'
    },
    {
        'question': """What part of his body does Micheal burn
        on a George Foreman grill:""",
        'answers': ['a) Hand',
                    'b) Tongue',
                    'c) Foot'],
        'correct': 'c'
    },
    {
        'question': 'What serial killer is mentioned throughout the series:',
        'answers': ['a) Scranton Strangler',
                    'b) Killer Kree',
                    'c) Violent Vic'],
        'correct': 'a'
    },
    {
        'question': 'Where did Jim and Pam go on their honey moon?:',
        'answers': ['a) Italy',
                    'b) Spain',
                    'c) Puerto Rico'],
        'correct': 'c'
    },
    {
        'question': 'Who is Angela and Dwights sons godfather?:',
        'answers': ['a) Senator Lipton',
                    'b) Oscar',
                    'c) Jim'],
        'correct': 'b'
    },
    {
        'question': 'Which of the following is a quote from Stanley?:',
        'answers': ['a) Did I stutter?',
                    'b) Did I sneeze?',
                    'c) Did I shout?'],
        'correct': 'a'
    },
    {
        'question': 'What kind of animal got loose in the office?:',
        'answers': ['a) Pigeon',
                    'b) Bat',
                    'c) Cat'],
        'correct': 'b'
    },
    {
        'question': 'How many cats does Angela have:',
        'answers': ['a) 13',
                    'b) 17',
                    'c) 23'],
        'correct': 'b'
    },
    {
        'question': 'How many seasons was Micheal Scott on The Office:',
        'answers': ['a) 5',
                    'b) 6',
                    'c) 7'],
        'correct': 'c'
    },
    {
        'question': 'What was Stanleys wifes name',
        'answers': ['a) Annie',
                    'b) Teri',
                    'c) Cheryl'],
        'correct': 'b'
    },
    {
        'question': 'Where is The Office set?',
        'answers': ['a) Scranton',
                    'b) Hunstvile',
                    'c) The Woodlands'],
        'correct': 'a'
    },
    {
        'question': 'How many children did Jim and Pam have?:',
        'answers': ['a) 2',
                    'b) 3',
                    'c) 4'],
        'correct': 'a'
    },
    {
        'question': 'What was Dwights Farm named?:',
        'answers': ['a) Schrute Farms',
                    'b) Beet Project',
                    'c) Mo and Dwight'],
        'correct': 'a'
    },
    {
        'question': 'Where did Roy take Pam on their first date?:',
        'answers': ['a) Minor league hockey game',
                    'b) The movies',
                    'c) A nice dinner'],
        'correct': 'a'
    },
    {
        'question': 'What is the name of Creeds blog?:',
        'answers': ['a) My naughty list',
                    'b) Creed thoughts',
                    'c) Dear Diary'],
        'correct': 'b'
    },
    {
        'question': 'What does Pam steal in the first season?:',
        'answers': ['a) Staples',
                    'b) Post it notes',
                    'c) Paper clips'],
        'correct': 'b'
    },
    {
        'question': 'Who dates Pams mother?',
        'answers': ['a) Creed',
                    'b) Micheal',
                    'c) Toby'],
        'correct': 'b'
    },
    {
        'question': 'What does Dwights family farm produce?:',
        'answers': ['a) Potatoes',
                    'b) Carrots',
                    'c) Beets'],
        'correct': 'c'
    },
    {
        'question': 'Who bought Micheals "Worlds Best Boss" mug:',
        'answers': ['a) Dwight',
                    'b) Jim',
                    'c) Micheal'],
        'correct': 'c'
    },
    {
        'question': 'What food is Kevin forced to eat?',
        'answers': ['a) Beets',
                    'b) Broccoli',
                    'c) Potatoe'],
        'correct': 'b'
    },
    {
        'question': 'Where does Jim propose to Pam??',
        'answers': ['a) A gas station',
                    'b) A fancy dinner',
                    'c) At the fireworks'],
        'correct': 'a'
    }
]